The Primary Source UP030
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
The Primary Source
1982 -- 2012
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Media Advocacy Board
UP030
2.0 Linear Feet
5 Volumes
231 Digital Object(s)
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series and grouped by calendar year through 2006, then by academic year.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains monthly issues of The Primary Source from 1982-1992, thereafter biweekly issues. It is a journal of conservative thought at Tufts, with articles written and compiled by Tufts students. As of March 2014, the website of the student organization (as well as older versions accessible through the Wayback Machine/Internet Archives) includes an archives of old Primary Source issues. However, some issues online have different dates on their covers and include fewer/different? articles then the original print issues available in this collection. The online version of the controversial December 6 2006 issue does not include the racist and sexist Christmas songs that were part of the paper issue and that had triggered national and local uproar and opposition at the time.
- Primary Source, 1982 -- 2012; UP030.001; 2.0 Linear Feet; 5 Volumes; 231 Digital Object(s)
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains issues of The Primary Source. It is a journal of conservative thought at Tufts, with articles written and compiled by Tufts students.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - 1982 Calendar Year, UP030.001.001
    - Primary Source, 1982-09; UP030.001.001.00001 (Box UP030 Shared 1)
      Volume, issue
      1, 1
    - Primary Source, 1982-10; UP030.001.001.00002 (Box UP030 Shared 1)
      1, 2
    - Primary Source, 1982-11; UP030.001.001.00003 (Box UP030 Shared 1)
      1, 3
    - Primary Source, 1982-12; UP030.001.001.00004 (Box UP030 Shared 1)
      1, 4
  - 1983 Calendar Year, UP030.002.001
    - Primary Source, 1983-02; UP030.002.001.00005 (Box UP030 Shared 1)
      1, 5
    - Primary Source, 1983-03; UP030.002.001.00006 (Box UP030 Shared 1)
      1, 6
    - Primary Source, 1983-04; UP030.002.001.00007 (Box UP030 Shared 1)
      1, 7
    - Primary Source, 1983-05; UP030.002.001.00008 (Box UP030 Shared 1)
      1, 8
    - Primary Source, 1983-09; UP030.002.001.00009 (Box UP030 Shared 1)
      2, 1
    - Primary Source, 1983-10; UP030.002.001.00010 (Box UP030 Shared 1)
      2, 2
    - Primary Source, 1983-11; UP030.002.001.00011 (Box UP030 Shared 1)
      2, 3
    - Primary Source, 1983-12; UP030.002.001.00012 (Box UP030 Shared 1)
      2, 4
  - 1984 Calendar Year, UP030.003.001
    - Primary Source, 1984-02; UP030.003.001.00013 (Box UP030 Shared 1)
      2, 5
    - Primary Source, 1984-03; UP030.003.001.00014 (Box UP030 Shared 1)
      2, 6
    - Primary Source, 1984-04; UP030.003.001.00015 (Box UP030 Shared 1)
      2, 7
    - Primary Source, 1984-05; UP030.003.001.00016 (Box UP030 Shared 1)
      2, 8
    - Primary Source, 1984-09; UP030.003.001.00017 (Box UP030 Shared 1)
      3, 1
    - Primary Source, 1984-10; UP030.003.001.00018 (Box UP030 Shared 1)
      3, 2
    - Primary Source, 1984-11; UP030.003.001.00019 (Box UP030 Shared 1)
      3, 3
    - Primary Source, 1984-12; UP030.003.001.00020 (Box UP030 Shared 1)
      3, 4
  - 1985 Calendar Year, UP030.004.001
    - Primary Source, 1985-02; UP030.004.001.00021 (Box UP030 Shared 1)
      3, 5
    - Primary Source, 1985-03; UP030.004.001.00022 (Box UP030 Shared 1)
      3, 6
    - Primary Source, 1985-04; UP030.004.001.00023 (Box UP030 Shared 1)
      3, 7
    - Primary Source, 1985-05; UP030.004.001.00024 (Box UP030 Shared 1)
      3, 8
    - Primary Source, 1985-09; UP030.004.002.00001 (Box UP030 Shared 2)
      4, 1
    - Primary Source, 1985-10; UP030.004.002.00002 (Box UP030 Shared 2)
      4, 2
    - Primary Source, 1985-12; UP030.004.002.00003 (Box UP030 Shared 2)
      4, 3
  - 1986 Calendar Year, UP030.005.001
    - Primary Source, 1986-03; UP030.005.002.00004 (Box UP030 Shared 2)
      4, 4
    - Primary Source, 1986-04; UP030.005.002.00005 (Box UP030 Shared 2)
      4, 5
    - Primary Source, 1986-10; UP030.005.002.00006 (Box UP030 Shared 2)
      5, 1
    - Primary Source, 1986-11; UP030.005.002.00007 (Box UP030 Shared 2)
      5, 2
    - Primary Source, 1986-12; UP030.005.002.00008 (Box UP030 Shared 2)
      5, 3
  - 1987 Calendar Year, UP030.006.001
    - Primary Source, 1987-03; UP030.006.002.00009 (Box UP030 Shared 2)
      5, 4
    - Primary Source, 1987-04; UP030.006.002.00010 (Box UP030 Shared 2)
      5, 5
    - Primary Source, 1987-10; UP030.006.003.00001 (Box UP030 Shared 3)
      6, 1
  - 1988 Calendar Year, UP030.007.001
    - Primary Source, 1988-02; UP030.007.003.00002 (Box UP030 Shared 3)
      6, 2
    - Primary Source, 1988-03; UP030.007.003.00003 (Box UP030 Shared 3)
      6, 3
    - Primary Source, 1988-04; UP030.007.003.00004 (Box UP030 Shared 3)
      6, 4
    - Primary Source, 1988-05; UP030.007.003.00005 (Box UP030 Shared 3)
      6, 5
    - Primary Source, 1988-09; UP030.007.003.00006 (Box UP030 Shared 3)
      7, 1
    - Primary Source, 1988-11; UP030.007.003.00007 (Box UP030 Shared 3)
      7, 2
    - Primary Source, 1988-12; UP030.007.003.00008 (Box UP030 Shared 3)
      7, 3
  - 1989 Calendar Year, 1989 -- 1990; UP030.008.001
    - Primary Source, 1989-03; UP030.008.003.00009 (Box UP030 Shared 3)
      7, 5
    - Primary Source, 1989-04; UP030.008.003.00010 (Box UP030 Shared 3)
      7, 6
    - Primary Source, 1989-08; UP030.008.003.00011 (Box UP030 Shared 3)
      8, 1
    - Primary Source, 1989-10; UP030.008.003.00012 (Box UP030 Shared 3)
      8, 2
    - Primary Source, 1989-11; UP030.008.003.00013 (Box UP030 Shared 3)
      8, 3
    - Primary Source, 1989 -- 1990; UP030.008.003.00014 (Box UP030 Shared 3)
      Holiday Issue.
      8, 4
  - 1990 Calendar Year, UP030.009.001
    - Primary Source, 1990-02; UP030.009.004.00001 (Box UP030 Shared 4)
      8, 5
    - Primary Source, 1990-03; UP030.009.004.00002 (Box UP030 Shared 4)
      8, 6
    - Primary Source, 1990-04; UP030.009.004.00003 (Box UP030 Shared 4)
      8, 7
    - Primary Source, 1990-09; UP030.009.004.00004 (Box UP030 Shared 4)
      9, 1
    - Primary Source, 1990-10; UP030.009.004.00005 (Box UP030 Shared 4)
      9, 2
    - Primary Source, 1990-11; UP030.009.004.00006 (Box UP030 Shared 4)
      9, 3
    - Primary Source, 1990-12; UP030.009.004.00007 (Box UP030 Shared 4)
      9, 4
  - 1991 Calendar Year, UP030.010.001
    - Primary Source, 1991-01; UP030.010.004.00008 (Box UP030 Shared 4)
    - Primary Source, 1991-02; UP030.010.004.00009 (Box UP030 Shared 4)
      9, 5
    - Primary Source, 1991-03; UP030.010.004.00010 (Box UP030 Shared 4)
      9, 6
    - Primary Source, 1991-04; UP030.010.004.00011 (Box UP030 Shared 4)
      9, 7
    - Primary Source, 1991-09; UP030.010.004.00012 (Box UP030 Shared 4)
      10, 1
    - Primary Source, 1991-10; UP030.010.004.00013 (Box UP030 Shared 4)
      10, 2
    - Primary Source, 1991-11; UP030.010.004.00014 (Box UP030 Shared 4)
      10, 3
    - Primary Source, 1991-12; UP030.010.004.00015 (Box UP030 Shared 4)
      10, 4
  - 1992 Calendar Year, UP030.011.001
    - Primary source, 1992-02; UP030.011.004.00016 (Box UP030 Shared 4)
      10, 5
      publication
    - Primary source, 1992-03; UP030.011.004.00017 (Box UP030 Shared 4)
      10, 6
    - Primary source, ten year anniversary issue, 1992; UP030.011.004.00018 (Box UP030 Shared 4)
    - Primary Source, 1992-09-03; UP030.011.005.00001 (Volume UP030 Shared 5)
      11, 1
    - Primary Source, 1992-09-17; UP030.011.005.00002 (Volume UP030 Shared 5)
      11, 2
    - Primary Source, 1992-09-30; UP030.011.005.00003
      11, 3
    - Primary Source, 1992-10-14; UP030.011.005.00004 (Volume UP030 Shared 5)
      11, 4
    - Primary Source, 1992-10-28; UP030.011.005.00005 (Volume UP030 Shared 5)
      11, 5
    - Primary Source, 1992-11-30; UP030.011.005.00006 (Volume UP030 Shared 5)
      11, 6
    - Primary Source, 1992-12-16; UP030.011.005.00007
      11, 7
  - 1993 Calendar Year, UP030.012.001
    - Primary Source, 1993-01-27; UP030.012.005.00008 (Volume UP030 Shared 5)
      XI, 8
    - Primary Source, 1993-02-10; UP030.012.005.00009 (Volume UP030 Shared 5)
      XI, 9
    - Primary Source, 1993-02-24; UP030.012.005.00010 (Volume UP030 Shared 5)
      XI, 10
    - Primary Source, 1993-03-10; UP030.012.005.00011 (Volume UP030 Shared 5)
      XI, 11
    - Primary Source, 1993-04-07; UP030.012.005.00012 (Volume UP030 Shared 5)
      XI, 12
    - Primary Source, 1993-04-21; UP030.012.005.00013 (Volume UP030 Shared 5)
      XI, 13
    - Primary Source, 1993-09-01; UP030.012.005.00014 (Volume UP030 Shared 5)
      XII, 1
    - Primary Source, 1993-09-15; UP030.012.005.00015 (Volume UP030 Shared 5)
      XII, 2
    - Primary Source, 1993-09-29; UP030.012.005.00016 (Volume UP030 Shared 5)
      XII, 3
    - Primary Source, 1993-10-13; UP030.012.005.00017 (Volume UP030 Shared 5)
      XII, 4
    - Primary Source, 1993-10-27; UP030.012.005.00018 (Volume UP030 Shared 5)
      XII, 5
    - Primary Source, 1993-11-10; UP030.012.005.00019 (Volume UP030 Shared 5)
      XII, 6
    - Primary Source, 1993-12-08; UP030.012.005.00020 (Volume UP030 Shared 5)
      XII, 7
  - 1994 Calendar Year, UP030.013.001
    - Primary Source, 1994-01-26; UP030.013.005.00021 (Volume UP030 Shared 5)
      XII, 8
    - Primary Source, 1994-02-09; UP030.013.005.00022 (Volume UP030 Shared 5)
      Bound after issue 10.
      XII, 9
    - Primary Source, 1994-02-23; UP030.013.005.00023 (Volume UP030 Shared 5)
      XII, 10
    - Primary Source, 1994-03-09; UP030.013.005.00024 (Volume UP030 Shared 5)
      XII, 11
    - Primary Source, 1994-04-06; UP030.013.005.00025 (Volume UP030 Shared 5)
      XII, 12
    - Primary Source, 1994-04-21; UP030.013.005.00026 (Volume UP030 Shared 5)
      XII, 13
    - Primary source, 1994-08-31; UP030.013.006.00001 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, 1994-09-15; UP030.013.006.00002 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, 1994-09-29; UP030.013.006.00003 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary Source, 1994-10-13; UP030.013.006.00004
    - Primary source, 1994-10-31; UP030.013.006.00005 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, 1994-11-10; UP030.013.006.00006 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, 1994-12-01; UP030.013.006.00007 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, 1994-12-15; UP030.013.006.00008 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
  - 1995 Calendar Year, UP030.014.001
    - Primary source, 1995-01-26; UP030.014.006.00009 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, 1995-02-09; UP030.014.006.00010 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, 1995-02-23; UP030.014.006.00011 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, 1995-03-09; UP030.014.006.00012 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, 1995-04-06; UP030.014.006.00013 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, 1995-04-27; UP030.014.006.00014 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, 1995-08-30; UP030.014.006.00015 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, 1995-09-14; UP030.014.006.00016 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, 1995-09-28; UP030.014.006.00017 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, 1995-10-12; UP030.014.006.00018 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, 1995-10-30; UP030.014.006.00019 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, 1995-11-16; UP030.014.006.00020 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
  - 1996 Calendar Year, UP030.015.001
    - Primary source, 1996-01-25; UP030.015.006.00021 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, 1996-02-08; UP030.015.006.00022 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, 1996-02-29; UP030.015.006.00023 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, 1996-04-04; UP030.015.006.00024 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, 1996-04-18; UP030.015.006.00025 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, 1996-05-02; UP030.015.006.00026 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, 1996-08-28; UP030.015.006.00027 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, 1996-09-12; UP030.015.006.00028 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, 1996-09-26; UP030.015.006.00029 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, 1996-10-10; UP030.015.006.00030 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, 1996-10-31; UP030.015.006.00031 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, 1996-11-21; UP030.015.006.00032 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, 1996-12-12; UP030.015.006.00033 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
  - 1997 Calendar Year, UP030.016.001
    - Primary source, January 30, 1997; UP030.016.006.00034 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, February 13, 1997; UP030.016.006.00035 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, February 27, 1997; UP030.016.006.00036 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, March 13, 1997; UP030.016.006.00037
    - Primary source, April 3, 1997; UP030.016.006.00038 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, April 17, 1997; UP030.016.006.00039
    - Primary source, August 27, 1997; UP030.016.006.00040
    - Primary source, September 11, 1997; UP030.016.006.00041 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, September 24, 1997; UP030.016.006.00042
    - Primary source, October 9, 1997; UP030.016.006.00043 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, November 6, 1997; UP030.016.006.00044 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, December 1, 1997; UP030.016.006.00045 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, December 11, 1997; UP030.016.006.00046 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
  - 1998 Calendar Year, UP030.017.001
    - Primary source, January 29, 1998; UP030.017.006.00047 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, February 12, 1998; UP030.017.006.00048 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, February 26, 1998; UP030.017.006.00049 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, April 2, 1998; UP030.017.006.00050 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, graduation, 1998; UP030.017.006.00051 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, orientation, 1998; UP030.017.006.00052 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, September 17, 1998; UP030.017.006.00053 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, October 1, 1998; UP030.017.006.00054 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, October 15, 1998; UP030.017.006.00055 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, November 5, 1998; UP030.017.006.00056 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, November 18, 1998; UP030.017.006.00057 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, December 10, 1998; UP030.017.006.00058 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
  - 1999 Calendar Year, UP030.018.001
    - Primary source, January 28, 1999; UP030.018.006.00059 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, February 11, 1999; UP030.018.006.00060 (Volume UP030 Shared 6)
    - Primary source, March 11, 1999; UP030.018.007.00001 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, April 8, 1999; UP030.018.007.00002 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, graduation, 1999; UP030.018.007.00003 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, orientation, 1999; UP030.018.007.00004 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, September 16, 1999; UP030.018.007.00005 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, September 30, 1999; UP030.018.007.00006 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, October 14, 1999; UP030.018.007.00007 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, October 28, 1999; UP030.018.007.00008 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, November 18, 1999; UP030.018.007.00009 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, December 9, 1999; UP030.018.007.00010 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
  - 2000 Calendar Year, 2000 -- 2001; UP030.019.001
    - Primary source, February 3, 2000; UP030.019.007.00011 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, February 17, 2000; UP030.019.007.00012 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, March 2, 2000; UP030.019.007.00013
    - Primary source, April 1, 2000; UP030.019.007.00014
    - Primary source, April 6, 2000; UP030.019.007.00015 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, graduation, 2000; UP030.019.007.00016 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, orientation, 2000; UP030.019.007.00017 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, September 21, 2000; UP030.019.007.00018 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, October 12, 2000; UP030.019.007.00019 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, October 26, 2001; UP030.019.007.00020 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, November 16, 2000; UP030.019.007.00021 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, December 7, 2000; UP030.019.007.00022 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
  - 2001 Calendar Year, UP030.020.001
    - Primary source, February 1, 2001; UP030.020.007.00023 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, February 14, 2001; UP030.020.007.00024 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, March 1, 2001; UP030.020.007.00025 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, March 15, 2001; UP030.020.007.00026 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, April 5, 2001; UP030.020.007.00027 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, spring, 2001; UP030.020.007.00028 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, Graduation, 2001; UP030.020.007.00029 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, Orientation, 2001; UP030.020.007.00030 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, September 27, 2001; UP030.020.007.00031 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, October 11, 2001; UP030.020.007.00032 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, October 25, 2001; UP030.020.007.00033 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, November 22, 2001; UP030.020.007.00034 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, December 6, 2001; UP030.020.007.00035 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
  - 2002 Calendar Year, UP030.021.001
    - Primary source, January 31, 2002; UP030.021.007.00036 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, February 14, 2002; UP030.021.007.00037 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, February 28, 2002; UP030.021.007.00038 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, commencement, 2002; UP030.021.007.00039 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, April 4, 2002; UP030.021.007.00040 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, August 28, 2002; UP030.021.007.00041 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, September 11, 2002; UP030.021.007.00042 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, 20th anniversary, 2002; UP030.021.007.00043 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, October 10, 2002; UP030.021.007.00044 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, October 31, 2002; UP030.021.007.00045 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, November 21, 2002; UP030.021.007.00046 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, December 11, 2002; UP030.021.007.00047 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary Source, April 30, 2002; UP030.021.007.00067
      Digital copy only.
      20, 10
  - 2003 Calendar Year, UP030.022.001
    - Primary source, January 30, 2003; UP030.022.007.00048 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, February 14, 2003; UP030.022.007.00049 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, February 26, 2003; UP030.022.007.00050
    - Primary source, March 12, 2003; UP030.022.007.00051 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, April 3, 2003; UP030.022.007.00052 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, April 17, 2003; UP030.022.007.00053 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, May 18, 2003; UP030.022.007.00054 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, August 27, 2003; UP030.022.007.00055 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
      Orientation Issue
    - Primary source, September 18, 2003; UP030.022.007.00056 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, October 16, 2003; UP030.022.007.00057 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, October 30, 2003; UP030.022.007.00058 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, November 20, 2003; UP030.022.007.00059 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, December 10, 2003; UP030.022.007.00060 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
  - 2004 Calendar Year, UP030.023.001
    - Primary source, February 12, 2004; UP030.023.007.00061 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, February 26, 2004; UP030.023.007.00062 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, March 18, 2004; UP030.023.007.00063 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, April 8, 2004; UP030.023.007.00064 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, April 22, 2004; UP030.023.007.00065 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary source, May 23, 2004; UP030.023.007.00066 (Volume UP030 Shared 7)
    - Primary Source, September 1, 2004; UP030.023.008.00001 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
    - Primary Source, September 23, 2004; UP030.023.008.00002 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
    - Primary Source, October 7, 2004; UP030.023.008.00003 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
    - Primary Source, October 21, 2004; UP030.023.008.00004 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
    - Primary Source, November 10, 2004; UP030.023.008.00005 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
    - Primary Source, December 9, 2004; UP030.023.008.00006 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
    - Primary source, March 11, 2004; UP030.023.DO.00001
  - 2005 Calendar Year, UP030.024.001
    - Primary Source, February 3, 2005; UP030.024.008.00007 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
    - Primary Source, February 16, 2005; UP030.024.008.00008 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
    - Primary Source, March 3, 2005; UP030.024.008.00009 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
    - Primary Source, March 17, 2005; UP030.024.008.00010 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
    - Primary Source, April 14, 2005; UP030.024.008.00011 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
    - Primary Source, April 21, 2005; UP030.024.008.00012 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
    - Primary Source, May 22, 2005; UP030.024.008.00013 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
      Commencement 2005
    - Primary Source, August 31, 2005; UP030.024.008.00014 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
    - Primary Source, September 29, 2005; UP030.024.008.00015 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
    - Primary Source, October 20, 2005; UP030.024.008.00016 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
    - Primary Source, November 3, 2005; UP030.024.008.00017 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
    - Primary Source, November 16, 2005; UP030.024.008.00018 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
    - Primary Source, December 8, 2005; UP030.024.008.00019 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
  - 2006 Calendar Year, UP030.025.001
    - Primary Source, February 1, 2006; UP030.025.008.00020 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
    - Primary Source, February 13, 2006; UP030.025.008.00021 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
    - Primary Source, March 1, 2006; UP030.025.008.00022 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
    - Primary Source, March 15, 2006; UP030.025.008.00023 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
    - Primary Source, April 5, 2006; UP030.025.008.00024 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
      Arts issue.
    - Primary Source, April 12, 2006; UP030.025.008.00025 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
    - Primary Source, May 21, 2006; UP030.025.008.00026 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
      Commencement 2006
    - Primary Source, August 30, 2006; UP030.025.008.00027 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
      25 On Our Silver Anniversary
    - Primary Source, Sept. 13, 2006; UP030.025.008.00028 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
      25, 2
    - Primary Source, Sept. 27, 2006; UP030.025.008.00029 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
      25, 3
    - Primary Source, Oct. 18, 2006; UP030.025.008.00030 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
      25, 4
    - Primary Source, Nov. 1, 2006; UP030.025.008.00031 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
      25, 5
    - Primary Source, Nov. 15, 2006; UP030.025.008.00032 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
    - Primary Source, December 6, 2006; UP030.025.008.00033 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
      25, 7
  - 2007 Spring and 2007-2008 Academic Year, UP030.026.001
    - Primary Source, January 24, 2007; UP030.026.008.00034 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
      25, 8
    - Primary Source, February 14, 2007; UP030.026.008.00035 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
      25, 9